

# Khaoula El Mourtagi

#### **PERFIL**

I have been trained to take the initiative as well as work in team. I have always been patient and determined. My pursue right now is to join a reputated company to gain the pilars of experience in which to build upon to later contribute bringing great value to the company.

#### CONTACTO

khaoula.ems@gmail.com

(+34)657309946

khaoulaems.github.io

in www.linkedin.com/in/khaoula-sayed

github.com/khaoulaems

#### **EXPERIENCIA LABORAL**

## FRAGRANCE SALES ASSOCIEATE

CHRISTIAN DIOR PARFUMS, ARMANI, BULGARI, GYVENCHY & KENZO

2017-2020

I worked in the sales sector, carrying out the weekly objectives i had set, as well as the accounting of the products that were sold. It was essential for me to use my linguistic skills especially english, arabic and spanish. My capacity for expressiveness and conviction, to obtain the highest number of sales. Knowing the needs of customers and being able to satisfy them was one of the main requirements, which is why the extensive knowledge of the sector and problem solving was a very useful tool.

# MATHS TEACHER

FREELANCE 2016-2018

I taught kids between 16-18 years old. I provided them with a personalized set of exercises that I would prepare based on previous studies. I had to go through many lessons to know the details of topics such as: Advanced Calculus, Linear Algebra and general problem solving techniques. I applied real world examples in order for them to see the need of knowing each of the latter mentioned topics as something worth learning.

#### EDUCACIÓN

# COMPUTER ENGINEERING & BUSINESS MANAGEMENT UNIVERSITY CARLOS III MADRID

Team work

2017-2023

Leadership



### LANGUAGES

Arabic

Spanish

English

French